My Device In this video we are going to look at
ICICI Lombard, the
pure sequence topic is SSC number,
but as you know
we focus more on trading, so
for this we will first
click on the difficult time on the long term, so
if I show you its trend is a
long term trend,
look at this, it is
not as clear that one it
broke from the Mita for Close,
after that it is continuously supporting the straight line, so
after this we will do it on Delhi
time,
this is our Delhi test,
if you see, if you see, there
is a support here, proper, where
this resistance falls,
today I will show you by drawing, first
see this, register space here,
register here, this break is given 11 test or some points,
then near Dumri Ghat railway line,
Andher
Rafiq, this train is near and
despite the train line, if you
look here, you will see that this resistance is currently
supporting here and on the straight line,
here we have  Double confirmation
sadly, there is a support and resistance support.
I have broken a register and now it is taking support on
that, as you know, you must have
known that if there is a
register back, then that tester
takes support on that, that becomes support,
that happened here also, this register back is
taking support here, the second
confirmation we have is that it is
taking support on the print line, a long-term time trend line as well,
if I tell you
that the
minimum return that this stock can give,
it can give around 10% in the first week, it
is a very good stock in the coming days, if 2
and moving averages are applied then you can see, as
you will see, the green candle has formed well,
here it is
also taking support of 120 movie address,
so in this way this stock MLA system simple,
if I show you again by applying that favorite statement, then let us
see at what level it is
taking support,
one tax circle is 0.5%, as you
can see here at
105  But it is taking support which is very
good, it becomes an important support level,
if we
talk about the Register Singh Ranchi level, then you must be
seeing that it has been following the trend line, it had
failed in the world due to quantity, by muting it like this, the cross of
this flower supports the train line,
still it is supporting, if you have
its minimum, mostly up to 4 crores,
then here it
can go like this, if you press it like this, then it will be quite upcoming, until it does
not break in the long term, we
can keep it folded, so until it does
not break the straight line, we can keep it folded properly,
my dear, for the British such a body,
you have
three confirmations, four confirmations, the
first confirmation we have is that this Register is
taking support by backing, another one is that it
follows the trend because it is a long
term trend line, till now it had
folded and broken due to fit, when
it did not bounce back, again there are multiple
times as you can see, multiple
times  Recently multiple times it has
taken support here, secondly it has broken the 2012
s20 moving average which is seen forming a green candle here, the
fourth confirmation is as I
told you that the dance level was
0.5 before the replacement of 2015, if I
look at them here then I can see the 0.5
level which can be a very good strong
registration support next
in the coming days
and after
taking the loot click on two, this has happened,
now in this it is sorry,
now it can give 10 percent off in half an hour,
so its moment as I
told it can go through this way here,
then it can come here and give feedback, something like this,
thank you for watching,
default this is ours, I have four
confirmations to straighten this stock.